JONATHAN CHOI

☑jonchoi11@gmail.com 📞 (778) 995-4791 👂 Calgary, AB 🛮 in www.linkedin.com/in/jonathan-choi-0502 🗘 jon-choi

SUMMARY

Newly minted full-stack developer with 5 years of experience as a sous-chef and 10+ years of overall kitchen experience looking to expand an already vast skillset and continuously learn from industry professionals. A keen ability to learn quickly, to solve problems, and to work seamlessly with others fuelled a desired interest in web development where lies endless opportunities not only for career advancement, but also for personal fulfillment.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ruby/Rails

FRAMEWORKS/LIBRARIES

NodeJS, ReactJS, Express, jQuery, Ajax, EJS

DATABASES

SQL (PostgreSQL, MySQL), MongoDB

PROJECTS

Oct. 2021 Cryptoverse

A web application for everything crypto! See current news, statistics, market caps, etc.

Tech Stack: React.js, Redux Toolkit, Ant Design, Chart.js, Rapid Api

Oct. 2021 Recipes

A simple recipe app where searching for your next meal is the easiest.

Tech Stack: React, Node-Sass, Axios

Oct. 2021 Crew Launcher

Crew Launcher is a brand new, cutting-edge application that allows users to seamlessly manage their

businesses with the ability to quote and book new jobs on-site.

Tech Stack: Express, React, Node.js, Websockets

Sept. 2021 Scheduler

Web application using React where users can create, edit, or delete appointments with mentors.

Tech Stack: React, Axios, Storybook, Cypress, Node-sass

EDUCATION

July 2021 to Oct. 2021 Lighthouse Labs

Diploma

Full-Stack Web Development

Sept. 2010 to Apr. 2015 University of Victoria

2015 B.A. Sociology

Focus in Law and Social Control, Pop Culture, and Media

EMPLOYMENT

Apr. 2020 to June 2021 Inherit Designs Landscaping · Gardener/Landscaper · Cobble Hill, BC

- Planting, transplanting, and maintaining flowers, plants, and gardens

- Consulting with clients on landscape designs, plant selection, and care

- Installing hardscape and landscape features

- Learned how to operate all ground and gardening equipment safely and efficiently

Sept. 2015 to Mar. 2020 Corduroy Pie Company · Sous Chef · Vancouver, BC

- Creation of daily feature pizzas

- Meeting targets of food quality, safety, and cost management

- Training and scheduling staff

- Learned to work well and efficiently under vast amounts of pressure/stress